<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">DoItWithAndroid</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_task">Tasks</string>
    <string name="navigation_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_graphs">Stats</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_date_format" translatable="false">d.M.yyyy    HH:mm</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_priority_high">High</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_priority_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_priority_low">Low</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_deadline_pick_header">Pick deadline</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_title_reopen_task">Reopen Task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_title_edit_task">Edit Task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_title_add_task">Add Task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_title_empty">Please insert title of task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_description_empty">Please insert description of task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_duration_empty">Please insert duration of task</string>
    <string name="add_edit_task_deadline_empty">Please pick a deadline</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_all_task_succ">Great! You can complete all tasks!</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_all_task_fail">Try skipping low priorities. Then you can make it!</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_med_task_succ">Medium and higher tasks completable</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_med_task_fail">Skip medium task, focus on high!</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_high_task_succ">You can complete all high priority tasks</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_overview_high_task_fail">Oh, you cannot complete all high tasks. Consider changing deadlines</string>
    <string name="task_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="fragment_archived_tasks_cannot_update_task">Task cannot be updated</string>
    <string name="fragment_archived_tasks_reopen_task">Task reopened successfully</string>
    <string name="fragment_archived_tasks_task_not_reopen">Task not reopened</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_task_done">Task done! Good work!</string>
    <string name="complete_task">Complete task</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title_call_mom">Call mom</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title_call_mom_des">Tell mom to have a nice day</string>
    <string name="tutorial_buy_milk_title">Buy milk</string>
    <string name="tutorial_buy_milk_des">Buy the freshest milk I can get</string>
    <string name="tutorial_go_to_work_title">Go to work</string>
    <string name="tutorial_go_to_work_des">Make some money</string>
    <string name="hours_short" translatable="false">h</string>
    <string name="minutes_short" translatable="false">min</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_welcome_title">Welcome</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_welcome_des">Welcome to DoItWithAndroid, since this is your first run, lets take a look on how to use this awesome app</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_menu_des">This is the main menu, use it to go through application</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overall_lvl_title">Overall level</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overall_lvl_des">This is your level. You will earn experience by completing your tasks. Try to complete as many tasks as you can a become a high level effective person!</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_exp_title">Experience</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_exp_des">This is your current experience and experience you need to reach new level. Every new level will require more experience than the last, it will get harder over time, but you can do it!</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_time_remaining_title">Time remaining</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_time_remaining_des">This is your time remaining today. It is how much working hours you have till the end of your day. Timer will stop when you add task, because application assumes that you gave started working. When you complete task, timer will recalculate how much time left.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_todo_tasks_title">Tasks to do today</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_todo_tasks_des">There you can find tasks you should do today. You do not have to complete them in given order, order is just recommended. Every task have its own color based on its priority. RED means high, YELLOW is medium and GREEN is low. Experience gained per task is based on priority and its duration. When you complete task, simply swipe left to mark it as done.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_gray_tasks_title">Gray tasks</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_gray_tasks_des">Gray tasks are same as normal tasks, only difference is that when your tasks are grayed out, the current time is not within you working time. You can still complete task as usual, but planner will not count their duration to your working time left today, also their completion time will be same as their estimated time. Feel free to complete task out of your working time, planner will recalculate your working plan :)</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_more_parts_title">Tasks on more parts</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_more_parts_des">If you do not have enough working time left today to fit in the whole task or you have task that is longer than you daily hours, you will still see this task on today list if its relevant. Difference is, that you will see this task with number of percent, which represents the part that will be completed when you mark this task as done</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_title">Quick overview</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_des">If you swipe left on you current level, you will get to quick overview of your tasks. Here you cas see if you are able to get everything done within your deadlines.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_all_title">All tasks</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_all_des">If you see this line with green check - Great! You are able to complete all your tasks and do not miss any deadline. Try to complete tasks as soon as possible to see this one green as often as you can.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_med_title">Medium priority tasks</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_med_des">If all tasks overview goes to red and this line is still green, you do not have to worry much. This means that you are still able to complete all medium and high priority task and Do It With Android will prepare plan how to complete them with ease :). However if you see this line red, that means you are not able to complete all medium priority task, so you should start working more effectively or consider changin you priorities or deadlines.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_high_title">High priority tasks</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_tutorial_overview_high_des">If all other goes to red and high priority stays green, there is still hope. That means you are able to complete at least all your high priority tasks, planner will ignore lower priority tasks and will make you a plan to complete your important things. If you see this red, you are in a problem. Red means that you are not able to complete all your high priority tasks no matter what you do. You will have to work out of your working hours or you will have to change deadlines/priorities</string>
    <string name="level_fragment_progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="fragment_overview_line_experience">Experience gained</string>
    <string name="fragment_overview_bar_tasks_day">Tasks completed per day</string>
    <string name="fragment_overview_bar_tasks_month">Tasks completed per month</string>
    <string name="fragment_overview_pie_priority_ratio">Tasks priority ratio</string>
    <string name="overview_fragment_tutorial_statistics_title">Statistics</string>
    <string name="fragment_overview_statistics_des">Statistics screen is exactly what it sounds to be. You can see statistics about your progress, completed tasks and more. Just scroll down and look at your statistics :)</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_butt_tutorial_title">Run tutorial again?</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_dialog_tutorial">This action will close settings and will enable tutorial to run once again.  Do you really want to play tutorial again?</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_dialog_prod_time_title">Confirm your productivity time</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_dialog_prod_time_p1">Your productivity time is:</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_dialog_prod_time_p2">hours</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_dialog_prod_time_p3">minutes  Is that correct?</string>
    <string name="task_adapter_deadline_not_completable">This deadline cannot be met!</string>
    <string name="task_adapter_focus_task">You should focus on this task</string>
    <string name="basic_information">Basic information</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="deadline">Deadline</string>
    <string name="click_to_add_date">+ Click to add date...</string>
    <string name="priority">Priority</string>
    <string name="estimated_duration">Estimated duration</string>
    <string name="hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="start_time">Start Time</string>
    <string name="end_time">End Time</string>
    <string name="run_tutorial_again">Run tutorial again</string>
    <string name="welcome_and_do_it_with_android">Welcome and Do It With Android!</string>
    <string name="first_run_1_des">Thank you for installing this app. It will help you to do things more effectively and also it will help to stop procrastinating. Since this is your first run, we have to Do some things first to get you started.  I hope you will enjoy and you will improve your time management</string>
    <string name="first_run2_des">Information</string>
    <string name="first_run3_start_des">Please set the time you normally start working, that means when you are ready to start working, e.g. after you eat your breakfast and or you drink your first coffee.</string>
    <string name="first_run3_end_des">Enter the time you normally stop being productive, it should not be just before you go to bed, but the time you stop working e.g. before you have your dinner and go watch TV or even before you go to brush your teeth for someone who is really productive!</string>
    <string name="complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="fragment_home_nothing_to_do">Nothing to do now</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_all">All tasks</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_high">High</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_deadline_after">Some tasks are after their deadline</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_current_tasks">Current Tasks</string>
    <string name="fragment_tasks_archived_tasks">Archived Tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_welcome_title">Task screen</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_welcome_des">Welcome to task screen. There you can find all your tasks. From this screen you can add tasks, see status of every task and change current tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_tasks_title">Tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_tasks_des">Here you can see all of your unfinished tasks. You can see their title, description, deadline (fire icon), estimated duration (clock icon) and on some of them there is more information. You will learn about this in short time.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_parted_title">Partly completed tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_parted_des">When you complete just a part of your task (as you learnt on home screen) you will see how many percent of this task is completed as number with percentage and small progress under task.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_edit_title">Complete/delete/edit</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_edit_des">If you want to edit task long press on it. To complete task from this screen simply swipe RIGHT and to delete task swipe LEFT.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_deadline_after_title">Tasks after deadline</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_deadline_after_des">When you see the deadline icon (fire) with red color, that means that this task is after its deadline. You should revisit it, since planner do not count it in your current tasks plan.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_udnoable_title">Undoable tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_undoable_des">When fire turns into red flashing exclamation mark, that means this task can never meet its deadline, even if you skip lower priority tasks. There task will not show on your daily tasks, since we think that it is better to complete at least something within its deadline, than more tasks after deadlines. Try to revisit these tasks.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_focus_title">Focus recommendation</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_focus_des">If you see warning sign on tasks priority strip, that means you cannot complete all tasks within their deadlines. This warning sign shown by tasks means that you should focus on them as they have higher priority</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_archive_title">Archive</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_archive_des">When you tap on archive tab, you will get to archive. All completed tasks are stored here, you can see info about these tasks as when you completed it and what was its real duration (tasks completed out of your working time will have their estimated time written here). If you want to reopen task (in case that new task is similar or the task is repeating) simply tap on that task and change relevant data. If you swipe RIGHT you can delete task from archive.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_top_screen_title">Top screen info</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_top_screen_des">On top of the screen, you can see quick status of your tasks (same as on home screen) so you do not have to switch back to home to see status of your tasks</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_deadline_alert_title">Deadline alert</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_deadline_alert_des">If red exclamation mark appears in top status bar, that means some of your tasks are already after deadline so you should be aware of that.</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_call_mom_title">Call mom</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_call_mom_des">Tell mom to have a nice day</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_pay_bills_title">Pay bills</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_pay_bills_des">Pay bill for electricity</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_buy_milk_title">Buy milk</string>
    <string name="tasks_fragment_tutorial_buy_milk_des">Buy the freshest milk I can get</string>
    <string name="graph_legend_priority_high">High priority</string>
    <string name="graph_legend_priority_medium">Medium priority</string>
    <string name="graph_legend_priority_low">Low priority</string>
    <string name="graph_no_data">No data</string>
    <string name="do_it_with_android" translatable="false">Do It With Android</string>
    <string name="about_version">Version:</string>
    <string name="about_author_label">Author:</string>
    <string name="me" translatable="false">Jan Horáček</string>
    <string name="about_contact">Contact:</string>
    <string name="me_mail" translatable="false">horacek.94@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="about_awareness_title">Diclaimer</string>
    <string name="about_awareness_data">Please be aware that author is not responsible for any missed deadline using this application. Use this application at your own risk as you can still miss any of your deadlines with no author responsibility.</string>
    <string name="mail_subject">Do It With Android Feedback</string>
    <string name="mail_text">Hi I would like to report feedback on your app:</string>
    <string name="mail_choose">Choose an Email client :</string>


</resources>
